Guide to the Yale Summer and Special Programs Student Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale Summer and Special Programs student records
1940-2012
RU 125
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
232
The records consist of student records maintained by Yale Summer and Special Programs.
Yale Summer and Special Programs
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 15-C (YRG 15-C), Student records from Yale summer and special programs.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of student records maintained by Yale Summer and Special Programs.
Sensitive content in this finding aid has been redacted to prevent disclosure. Unredacted finding aid restricted to office of origin only.
College students; Yale Summer and Special Programs; Yale University -- Students
- Student records, 1948-1969; Accession 1981-A-033
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2045
  - 1948 - 1954 (Box 1)
  - 1955 - 1958 A-M (Box 2)
  - 1958 N-Z - 1960 A-King (Box 3)
  - 1960 Kinn-Z - 1961 (Box 4)
  - 1962 - 1963 A-F (Box 5)
  - 1963 G-Z - 1964 A-MeV (Box 6)
  - 1964 Mag-Z - 1965 A-Now (Box 7)
  - 1965 Nor-Z - 1966 A-Roo (Box 8)
  - 1966 Ros-Z - 1967 A-Saun (Box 9)
  - 1967 Sauo - 1968 Wae (Box 10)
  - 1968 Wah - 1969 (Box 11)
- Student records [microfilm], 1948-1969; Accession 1981-A-034
  - 1948-1960 (Reel 1)
  - 1961-1964 McVay (Reel 2)
  - 1964 Magistretti-1967 Becroft, 1964-1967 (Reel 3)
  - 1967 Beebe-1969, 1967-1969 (Reel 4)
- Student records, 1978; Accession 1983-A-049
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2054
  - A-J, 1978 (Box 1)
  - K-P, 1978 (Box 2)
  - R-Z, 1978 (Box 3)
- Student transcripts [microfilm], 1978-1982; Accession 1983-A-050 (Reel 1)
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2058
- Student records, 1970-1977; Accession 1983-A-112
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2053
  - 1970 A - Z (Box 1)
  - 1971 A - D (Box 1)
  - 1971 E - Z (Box 2)
  - 1972 A - L (Box 2)
  - 1972 M - Z (Box 3)
  - 1973 A - M (Box 3)
  - 1973 N - Z (Box 4)
  - 1974 A - P (Box 4)
  - 1974 Q - Z (Box 5)
  - 1975 A - R (Box 5)
  - 1975 S - Z (Box 6)
  - 1976 A - R (Box 6)
  - 1976 S - Z (Box 7)
  - 1977 A - Z (Box 7)
  - Security Microfilm
    - 1970 A - 1972 Bu (Reel 1)
    - 1972 By - 1973 Schm (Reel 2)
    - 1973 Schn - 1975 Markoff (Reel 3)
    - 1975 Markov - 1977 Z (Reel 4)
- Student records, 1978-1980; Accession 1987-A-015 (Box 2–12)
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2056
  Scope and Contents
  No online inventory. Paper inventory available in repository.
- Student applications, 1983; Accession 1988-A-082
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2059
  - Applications for College-level Summer Programs
    - A - Fa, 1983 (Box 1)
    - Fa - Le, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Li - Sch, 1983 (Box 3)
    - Sci - Z, 1983 (Box 4)
  - Applications for Intensive English Language Study (A - Z), 1983 (Box 5)
  - Applications and Administrative Files for "Elderhostel Summer Program (A-Z), 1983 (Box 6)
- Student records, 1985; Accession 1989-A-056 (Box 1–5)
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2061
  No inventory available.
- Student records, 1989; Accession 1993-A-017
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2065
  - Kupi, Adem, 1989 (Box 2)
- Student records, 1990; Accession 1994-A-063
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2066
  - McIntyre, John A., Jr., 1990 (Box 3)
  - Withdrawn
- Special student records, 1982-1991; Accession 1995-A-011
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2067
  - Non- Degree Special Students (Leave of Absence), 1988 -1991
  - Degree Special Students Alumni, 1982-1988
  - Withdrawn Non-Degree Special Students, 1988-1991
- Student records, 1991; Accession 1995-A-015
  - Karaki, Toshiharu, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 501)
  - Withdrawn Students: Ahn-Zises (Box 7)
- Student records, 1992; Accession 1996-A-001 (Box 1–4)
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2068
- Special programs student records, 1989-1994; Accession 1996-A-002
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2070
  - 0, Fall 93 (Box 1, Folder 129)
- Student records, 1993; Accession 1997-A-005
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2069
  Partial inventory available online only. Full paper inventory available in repository.
  - Withdraws/Rejects
- Special student records, 1966-1997; Accession 1998-A-072
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2073
  - Special alumni degree student records, 1966-1994 (Box 1–2)
  - Special non-degree student records, 1989-1997 (Box 3–4)
- Student records, 1994; Accession 1999-A-071 (Box 1–4)
- Student records, 1995; Accession 2000-A-031 (Box 1–4)
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2071
- Student records, 1996; Accession 2001-A-072 (Box 1–4)
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2072
- Student records, 1997; Accession 2002-A-121
  - Kanner, William (withdrawn), 1997 (Box 3, Folder 501)
- Student records, 1998; Accession 2003-A-066
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2074
- Student transcripts, circa 1960-1989; Accession 2003-A-163
  - Baumann, Robert F (Box 1, Folder 501)
  - Cox, Susan (Box 1, Folder 1751)
  - Gallant, Batya (Box 2, Folder 2876)
  - Hoyt, Judy (Box 2, Folder 3938)
  - Lamont, Hamilton Graham (Box 2, Folder 4969)
  - Mendillo, Emily Ann (Box 3, Folder 5985)
  - Plunkett, Regina St G. (Box 3, Folder 6993)
  - Serres, Terrence J (Box 3, Folder 7997)
  - Trout, Robert E (Box 4, Folder 8999)
- Student course records, circa 1920-1988; Accession 2004-A-033
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2064
  - Multiple Page Transcripts
    - A-H (Box 16)
    - I-R (Box 17)
    - R-Z (Box 18)
- Student records, 1999; Accession 2004-A-089
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2075
  - Mosquera, Daniel, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 501)
  - Withdrawn
- Shafer Scholarship records and student files of the Piano Institute, 1984-1998; Accession 2004-A-117
  - Shafer Scholarship
  - 1984 Admitted Students (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1986 Admitted Students (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1988 Admitted Students (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1990 Admitted Students (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Piano Institute
  - 1990 Piano Institute Student Information (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - 1991 Piano Institute Student Information (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Student records, 2000; Accession 2005-A-072
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2076
  - Munson, Nelsie, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 501)
  - Withdrawals
- Student transcripts, 1983-1984; Accession 2005-A-122
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2060
  Partial inventory only, contains only double-sided or multiple-paged records.
- Grade reports, 1940-1988; Accession 2005-A-149
  - Box 1 (Folder 44)
  - Maier Robert W Jr (Box 1, Folder 505)
  - Stolts Jack L (Box 2, Folder 1761)
- Student records, 2001; Accession 2006-A-119
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2077
  - McKenney, Tara, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 501)
  - Withdrawals
- Student records, 2002; Accession 2006-A-120
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2078
  - Martinez, Sara, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 501)
  - Withdrawals
- Auditing student records, 1985-1999; Accession 2006-A-125
- Student records, 2003-2004; Accession 2007-A-049
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2080
  - STARS 2003 Student Files (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Lee, Grace, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 498)
  - Withdrawals
  - Purcell, Caitlin, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 1743)
  - Withdrawals, 2004 (Box 14)
- Non-degree student records, 1993-2004; Accession 2007-A-121
- Student records, 2005; Accession 2008-A-089
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2081
  - Hsu, Ya-hwei, 2005 June - August (Box 4, Folder 501)
  - Withdrawals
  - Students who registered but did not attend
- Eli Whitney program student records, 2008; Accession 2009-A-037
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2084
  - Graduates
  - Withdrawals
- Student records, 2008; Accession 2009-A-040
  Restricted until January 1, 2084.
  - Hinds, Kumba, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 501)
  - No Shows
  - Withdrawals
- Non-Degree/program inactive student records, 1998-2006; Accession 2009-A-041
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2082
- Student records, 2007-2008; Accession 2010-A-031
  Restricted until January 1, 2084
  - 2007
    - Un-Fileable Items, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Koeing, Amy, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 501)
  - 2007 ELI program
  - 2007 No show/withdrawn
  - 2008
    - Unfileable Items, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 1688)
    - Ingram, Antonio, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 2188)
  - 2008 ELI program
  - 2008 No show/withdrawn
- Student records, 2012; Accession 2014-A-056
  Restricted until January 1, 2087
  - ELI
  - Active
    - Huttler, Alexandra, 2012 Summer (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - No-Show/Withdrawn
    - Zhang, Mingjian, 2012 Summer (Box 11, Folder 171)